Finding Aid for Charles A. Sink autographed photograph collection, 1894-1972
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Charles A. Sink autographed photograph collection 1894-1972
Sink, Charles A., collector.
9817 Aa 2
Charles A. Sink was president of University Musical Society. Photographs (mainly autographed portraits) of musical performers, many of whom appeared in performances of the University Musical Society.
568 photographs in 6 boxes
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was transferred from the University Musical Society (Donor no. 2996 ).
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Charles A. Sink was an Ann Arbor businessman and civic leader. He was also a long-time president of the University Musical Society, which was responsible for many of the musical program series performed in Ann Arbor at the University of Michigan. These included the May Festival, performances of the Choral Union, and the yearly presentation of Handel's Messiah.
The collection consists of photographs (mainly autographed portraits) given to Sink in his responsibility as president of the University Musical Society. There are over 550 photographs, most of them are 8" x 10" prints. They have been arranged into two alphabets, one for individual photographs and one for photographs which were originally in an album. The listing includes "see" and "see also" references so that every occurrence of a person can be located whether it is in a file for a different individual or located separately because of size. The exception to this is for some of the group photos for which the group is identified but individuals are not (or their signatures are not legible). Unidentified photographs (there are three) are in a folder at the beginning of Box 1. There is one photograph per folder unless otherwise indicated. Some of the multiples are duplicates.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Ann Arbor May Festival.; Caruso, Enrico, 1873-1921.; Farrar, Geraldine, 1882-1967.; Garden, Mary, 1874-1967.; Johnson, Thor.; Kreisler, Fritz, 1875-1962.; Moore, Grace, 1898-1947.; Maddy, Joseph E. (Joseph Edgar), 1891-1966.; Music festivals--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Musicians.; Orchestras.; Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985.; Ponselle, Rosa, 1897-1981.; Singers.; Sink, Charles A. (Charles Albert), 1879-1972.; Stanley, Albert A. (Albert Augustus), 1851-1932.; Stracciari, Riccardo.; Tucker, Richard, 1913-1975.; University of Michigan. University Musical Society.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Autographed Photographs
  - Unidentified
    - Woman with flowers, "Hartsook Photo" (Box 1)
    - Man with mustache, dated Sat., March 17 (Box 1)
    - String quartet: Sidney ?, Jack O'Brien, Philip ?, and ?, dated February 20, 1954 (Box 1)
      (photographer: Antony di Gesú, 1320 Madison Ave., New York)
  - Abbas, Phillip (Box 1)
  - Addison, Adele (Box 1)
  - Addison, Mabelle (Box 1)
  - Alberts, Eunice (Box 1)
  - Alcock, Merle (Box 1)
  - Althouse, Paul (Box 1)
  - Amato, Pasquale (Box 1)
  - America's Leading Impresarios "21 Club" dinner 1954 (Box 5)
    (oversize)
  - Anderson, Marian, 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Arden, Cecil (Box 1)
  - Arrau, Claudio (Box 1)
  - Babin, Victor (Box 1)
  - Baccaloni, Salvatore, 2 photographs (Box 1)
    (See also Box 5)
  - Bachauer, Gina, 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Bachaus, William (Box 1)
  - Badura-Skoda, Paul (Box 1)
  - Ballester, Vincent (Box 1)
  - Bampton, Rose (Box 1)
  - Barere, Simon (Box 1)
  - Baromeo, Chase "Sikes", 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Bartlett, Ethel (Box 1)
  - Bartók, Béla (Box 1)
  - Basiola, Mario (Box 1)
  - Bay, Emanuel (Box 1)
  - Beattie, Douglas (Box 1)
  - Beecham, Sir Thomas (Box 1)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig van (Box 1)
  - Bentzon, Johan (Box 1)
    (see Sink, Charles)
  - Blatt, Josef (Box 1)
    (see Tucker, Richard)
  - Bollinger, Anne (Box 1)
  - Bonci, Alessandro, 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Bonelli, Richard, 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Bonnet, M. Joseph (Box 1)
  - Borkh, Inge (Box 1)
  - Brailowsky, Alexander, 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Branzell, Karen (Box 1)
  - Braslav, Sophie (Box 1)
  - Brickner, Bernard R. (Box 1)
  - Brown, Anne (Box 1)
  - Brun, François-Julien (Box 1)
  - Budapest String Quartet, 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Burke, Hilda (Box 1)
  - Burton, Mr. & Mrs. M. L. (Box 1)
    (see Garden, Mary)
  - Busch, Fritz (Box 1)
  - Bustabo, Guila (Box 1)
  - Carr, Nancy (Box 1)
  - Caruso, Enrico, 3 photographs (Box 1)
  - Casadesus, Robert (Box 1)
  - Case, Anna, 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Castagna, Bruna (Box 1)
  - Caston, Saul (Box 1)
  - Chabay, Leslie (Box 1)
  - Chaliapin, Feodor (Box 1)
  - Chamlee, Mario, 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Chookasian, Lillian (Box 1)
  - Christian, Palmer (Box 1)
  - Christiansen, F. Melius, director, St. Olaf Choir (Box 1)
  - Clark, Mary Jane: Clark Harp Trio (Box 1)
  - Clark, Senator Roy (7th district) (Box 1)
  - Cluytens, Andre (Box 1)
  - Coppisus, F. L. (Box 1)
    (see Caruso, Enrico)
  - Cordon, Norman (Box 1)
  - Corona, Leonora (Box 5)
  - Cortot, Alfred (Box 1)
  - Courte, Robert (Box 1)
  - Crisler, Fritz (Box 1)
    (see Kreisler, Fritz)
  - Crooks, Richard (Box 1)
  - Curzon, Clifford (Box 1)
  - Damrosch, Walter, 4 photographs (Box 1)
  - Danise, Guiseppe (Box 1)
  - Davis, Agnes (Box 1)
  - Davis, Horace L. "Curly", 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Defauw, Désiré (Box 1)
  - De los Angeles, Victoria (Box 1)
  - De Luca, Guiseppe (Box 1)
  - De Pachman, Vladimir (Box 1)
  - Depaur's Infantry Chorus (Box 1)
  - De Segurola, Andres, 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Dirman, Rose (Box 1)
  - Doe, Doris (Box 1)
  - Dohnanyi, Ernö (Box 1)
  - Dorati, Antal (Box 1)
  - Doree, Doris (Box 1)
  - Duey, Philip (Box 1)
  - Dupré, Marcel (Box 1)
  - Dux, Claire (Box 1)
  - Easton, Florence, 2 photographs (Box 1)
  - Eddy, Nelson (Box 1)
  - Ellis, C. A. (Box 1)
    (see Farrar, Geraldine)
  - Elman, Mischa (Box 1)
  - Elmo, Cloe (Box 1)
  - Elokas, Ossi (Box 1)
  - Enesco, Georges (Box 1)
  - English Singers (Box 1)
  - Ericourt, Daniel (Box 1)
  - Erskine, John (Box 1)
  - Eustis, Edwina (Box 1)
  - Farrar, Geraldine, 3 photographs (Box 2)
    (see also Box 5)
  - Farrell, Eileen (Box 2)
  - Fellowes, Edmund H. (Box 2)
  - Feuermann, Emanuel (Box 2)
  - Fiedler, Arthur (Box 2)
  - Firkusny, Rudolf (Box 2)
  - Flagstad, Kirsten (Box 2)
  - Fleisher, Leon (Box 2)
  - Fowles, Ernest (Box 2)
  - Francescatti, Zino (Box 2)
  - Fredericks, Walter (Box 2)
  - Fremstad, Olive (Box 2)
  - Friedman, Ignaz (Box 2)
  - Gabrilowitsch, Ossip, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Gadski, Johanna (Box 2)
  - Galli-Curci, Amelita, 3 photographs (Box 2)
  - Garden, Mary, 3 photographs (Box 2)
  - Gates, Lucy, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Gerardy, Jean (Box 2)
  - Gershwin Festival (Box 2)
  - Gershwin, George (Box 2)
  - Giannini, Dusolina (Box 5)
  - Gigli, Beniamino, 4 photographs (Box 2)
  - Glaz, Hertha (Box 2)
  - Glenn, Carroll (Box 2)
  - Goldman, Edwin Franko (Box 2)
  - Golschmann, Vladimir (Box 2)
  - Goossens, Eugene (Box 2)
  - Gordon, Jeanne, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Grainger, Percy, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Graveure, Louis (Box 2)
  - Greenwell, Gean (Box 2)
  - Gustafson, William (Box 2)
  - Hagar, Emily Stokes (Box 2)
  - Hagen, Betty-Jean (Box 2)
  - Hamilton, James, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Hanson, Howard, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Harrell, Mack (Box 2)
  - Harrold, Orville (Box 2)
  - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 2)
    (see Ormandy, Eugene)
  - Haugh, Harold (Box 2)
  - Hayes, Roland (Box 2)
  - Heermann, Hugo (Box 2)
  - Heermann, Walter (Box 2)
  - Heifetz, Jascha (Box 2)
  - Hellwig, Judith (Box 2)
  - Hess, Myra, 3 photographs (Box 2)
  - Hilsberg, Alexander (Box 2)
  - Hines, Jerome, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Hinshaw, William Wade, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Hinkle, Florence (Box 2)
  - Hofmann, Josef, 3 photographs (Box 2)
  - Holst, Gustav (Box 2)
  - Homer, Louise, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Horowitz, Vladimir (Box 2)
  - Howland, William (Box 2)
  - Huberman, Bronislaw (Box 2)
  - Hutcheson, Ernest (Box 2)
  - Istomin, Eugene (Box 2)
  - Iturbi, José (Box 2)
  - Jagel, Frederick (Box 2)
  - James, Louis (Box 2)
  - Janis, Byron (Box 2)
    (see also Ormandy, Eugene)
  - Jaroff, Serge (Box 2)
  - Jarret, Howard (Box 2)
  - Jepson, Helen (Box 5)
  - Johnson, Edward (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Thor (Box 2)
    (see also Moore, Grace)
  - Johnston, Edward (R. E.) (Box 2)
  - Kapell, William (Box 2)
  - Kaskas, Anna (Box 2)
  - Keener, Suzanne (Box 2)
  - Kell, Reginald (Box 2)
    (see Reginald Kell Players)
  - Kelsey, ? (Box 2)
  - Kincaid, William (Box 2)
  - Kingston, Morgan (Box 5)
  - Knight, Felix (Box 2)
  - Koch, Raymund (Box 2)
  - Kochanski, Paul (Box 2)
  - Koshetz, Alexander (Box 2)
  - Koussevitzky, Serge, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Kraft, Arthur (Box 2)
  - Kreisler, Fritz, 4 photographs (Box 2)
  - Kubelik, Rafael (Box 2)
  - Kullman, Charles (Box 2)
  - Langdon-Davis, John (Box 2)
  - Laval, Jeanne (Box 2)
  - Lawrence, Marjorie (Box 2)
  - Lazaro, Hipolito (Box 2)
  - Lazzari, Carolina (Box 2)
  - Lazzari, Virgilio (Box 2)
  - Leginska, Ethel (Box 2)
  - Lehmann, Lotte (Box 2)
  - Lenska, Augusta (Box 2)
  - Leonard, Myrtle (Box 2)
  - Levant, Oscar (Box 2)
  - Levine, Josef (Box 2)
  - Leyssac, Paul (Box 2)
  - Lippe, Juliette (Box 5)
  - Lipton, Martha (Box 2)
  - List, Eugene (Box 2)
  - Litzenberg, Karl (Box 2)
  - Lloyd, David (Box 2)
  - Lockwood, Samuel (Box 2)
    (see University Symphony Orchestra)
  - London, George (Box 2)
  - Long, Carolyn (Box 2)
    (see Gershwin Festival)
  - Love, Mark (Box 2)
  - Luboshutz, Lea (Box 2)
  - Luboshutz, Pierre (Box 2)
    (see Nemenoff, Genia)
  - Maazel, Lorin (Box 3)
    (see also Gershwin Festival)
  - MacBeth, Florence (Box 3)
  - MacDowell, Edward, 2 photographs (Box 5)
  - MacMillan, Sir Ernest (Box 3)
  - MacWatters, Virginia (Box 3)
  - Maddy, Joseph E. (Box 3)
  - Maier, Guy (Box 3)
  - Mantovani (Box 3)
  - Mario, Queena (Box 3)
  - Marshall, Charles (Box 3)
  - Marshall, Lois (Box 3)
  - Martinelli, Giovanni (Box 3)
  - Martini, Nino (Box 5)
  - Mason, Edith, 2 photographs (Box 3)
  - Matzunauer, Margaret (Box 3)
  - May Festival, 3 photographs
    - First May Festival, University Hall May 19, 1894 (Box 3)
    - First May Festival audience in Hill Aud. May 14, 1913 (Box 3)
  - Mayer, Daniel (Box 3)
  - Maynor, Dorothy (Box 3)
  - McChesney, Ernest (Box 3)
  - McCollum, John (Box 3)
  - McCormack, John (Box 5)
  - McCoy, Lester (Box 3)
    (see also Tucker, Richard)
  - McDonald, Harl (Box 3)
  - McIntyre, Frank, 2 photographs (Box 3)
  - Meisle, Kathryn (Box 5)
  - Melchior, Lauritz (Box 3)
  - Menuhin, Yehudi (Box 3)
  - Meredith, Morley (Box 3)
  - Merriman, Nan (Box 3)
  - Milanov, Zinka (Box 3)
  - Milstein, Nathan, 2 photographs (Box 3)
  - Mitropoulos, Dimitri (Box 3)
  - Molinari, Bernardino (Box 5)
  - Montana, Marie (Box 3)
  - Monteux, Pierre (Box 3)
    (see also Koussevitzky, Serge)
  - Moore, Earl V. (Box 3)
  - Moore, Grace, 3 photographs (Box 3)
  - Moore, Mary (Box 3)
  - Morelli, Carlo (Box 3)
  - Morgan, Rhys (Box 3)
  - Morgana, Nina, 2 photographs (Box 3)
    (see also Caruso, Enrico)
    (see also oversize Box 5)
  - Morini, Erika (Box 3)
  - Moscona, Nicola (Box 3)
  - Moudry, Janice (Box 3)
  - Munch, Charles (Box 3)
  - Munsel, Patrice (Box 3)
  - Murphy, Lambert (Box 3)
  - Musical Art Quartet of New York, first annual Chamber Music Festival (Box 3)
  - Muzio, Claudia (Box 3)
  - Nadell, Rosalind (Box 3)
  - National Association of Concert Managers 1950, 1956, 3 photographs (Box 5)
  - Natzka, Oscar (Box 3)
  - Nelli, Herva (Box 3)
  - Nemenoff, Genia (Box 3)
  - Neveu, Jean and Ginette (Box 3)
  - Nikolaidi, Elena (Box 3)
  - Nosler, Maud (Box 3)
  - Novaes, Guiomar, 2 photographs (Box 3)
  - Novotna, Jarmila (Box 3)
  - Onegin, Sigrid, 2 photographs (Box 3)
  - Ormandy, Eugene, 7 photographs (Box 3)
  - Owen, Chloe (Box 3)
  - Paderewski, Ignace Jan, 3 photographs (Box 3)
    (see also Schelling, Ernest)
  - Paganini Quartet, 3 photographs (Box 3)
  - Panteleieff, Maxim (Box 3)
  - Parera, Valentine (Box 3)
    (see Moore, Grace)
  - Parkhurst, Adele (Box 3)
  - Patterson, Lee (Box 3)
    (see Maier, Guy)
  - Pease, James (Box 3)
  - Peebles, Joan (Box 3)
  - Peerce, Jan (Box 3)
  - Peralta, Frances (Box 3)
  - Peters, Roberta (Box 3)
  - Petri, Egon (Box 3)
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor (Box 3)
  - Pinza, Ezio (Box 3)
  - Pons, Lily (Box 3)
  - Ponselle, Rosa, 3 photographs (Box 3)
  - Posselt, Ruth (Box 3)
  - Potter, Howard (Box 3)
  - Prague Teachers Chorus (Box 3)
  - Pratt, Waldo S. (Box 3)
  - Primrose, William (Box 3)
  - Quartetto Italiano (Box 3)
  - Rabinof, Benno (Box 3)
  - Rachmaninoff, Serge, 2 photographs (Box 3)
  - Raisa, Rosa (Box 3)
  - Rankin, Nell (Box 3)
  - Recklin, Edward (Box 3)
  - Reed, Corinne Rider (Box 3)
  - Reginald Kell Players (Box 3)
  - Reiner, Fritz (Box 3)
  - Resnik, Regina (Box 3)
  - Reynolds, Eleanor (Box 3)
  - Ricci, Ruggiero (Box 3)
  - Robeson, Paul (Box 3)
  - Robertson, Rae (Box 3)
    (see Bartlett, Ethel)
  - Rodgers, Ruth (Box 3)
  - Rodzinski, Arthur (Box 3)
  - Roman, Stella (Box 3)
  - Rosenthal, Moritz (Box 3)
  - Ross, Stuart (Box 3)
    (see Ponselle, Rosa)
  - Roth Quartet (Box 3)
  - Rubinstein, Artur (Box 3)
  - Ruffo, Titta (Box 3)
  - Box 4 (Box 3)
  - Sanroma, J. M. (Box 3)
  - Santelmann, William (Box 3)
  - Sayao, Bidu (Box 3)
  - Scheib, Eleanor (Box 3)
  - Schelling, Ernest, 3 photographs (Box 3)
  - Schlegel, Carl (Box 3)
  - Schnabel, Artur (Box 3)
  - Schumann-Heink, Ernestine, 2 photographs (Box 3)
  - Schwarzkopf, Elisabeth (Box 3)
  - Scott, Henri (Box 3)
  - Scott, Norman (Box 3)
  - Seidel, Toscha, 2 photographs (Box 3)
  - Sembrich, Marcella, 2 photographs (Box 3)
  - Serkin, Rudolf, 2 photographs (Box 3)
  - Sevitzky, Fabien (Box 3)
  - Shaw, Robert (Box 3)
  - Siepi, Cesare (Box 3)
  - Sigma Alpha Iota Convention 1930 (Box 3)
  - "Sikes", Chase (Box 3)
    (see Baromeo, Chase)
  - Simon, Frank (Box 3)
  - Sink, Charles (Box 3)
    (for further images of Charles Sink see also Caruso, Enrico; Farrar, Geraldine; Garden, Mary; Johnson, Thor; Kreisler, Fritz; Moore, Grace; Ormandy, Eugene; Stracciari, Riccardo; Tucker, Richard)
    (see also Box 5 for Michigan Legislature, Senate Concurrent Resolution No. 8 memorial for Dr. Charles A. Sink, January 11, 1973)
  - Sink, Mr. & Mrs. Charles (Alva), 3 photographs (Box 3)
    (see also Ponselle, Rosa)
  - Slobodskaja, Oda (Box 3)
  - Smith, Carol (Box 3)
  - Smith, Kenneth, 2 photographs (Box 3)
  - Smith, Shirley (Box 3)
  - Socoloff, Sergei (Box 3)
  - Solomon (Box 3)
  - Somer, Hilde (Box 3)
  - Sousa, John Philip (Box 3)
  - Spalding, Albert (Box 3)
  - Sparkes, Lenora (Box 3)
  - Spencer, Janet (Box 4)
  - Spivakovsky, Tossy (Box 4)
  - Stanley, Albert A. (Box 4)
    (see also Farrar, Geraldine)
  - Steber, Eleanor (Box 4)
  - Steinway, Theodore (Box 4)
  - Sten, Suzanne (Box 4)
  - Stevens, Risë (Box 5)
  - Stock, Frederick A. (Box 4)
    (see also Szigeti, Joseph)
  - Stracciari, Riccardo, 3 photographs (Box 4)
  - Swarthout, Gladys (Box 5)
  - Svanholm, Set (Box 4)
  - Szantho, Enid (Box 4)
  - Szell, George (Box 4)
  - Szigeti, Joseph, 2 photographs (Box 4)
  - Tagliavini, Ferruccio (Box 4)
  - Tangeman, Nell (Box 4)
  - Tajo, Italo (Box 4)
  - Talley, Marion (Box 4)
  - Thebom, Blanche (Box 4)
  - Thomas, John Charles (Box 4)
  - Thorborg, Kerstin (Box 4)
  - Tibbett, Lawrence (Box 4)
  - Tittmann, Charles (Box 4)
  - Tokatyan, Armand (Box 4)
  - Tourel, Jennie (Box 4)
  - Traubel, Helen (Box 4)
  - Tucker, Richard, 2 photographs (Box 4)
  - Turner, Claramae (Box 4)
  - Tuxen, Erik (Box 4)
  - Uninsky, Alexander (Box 4)
  - University Symphony Orchestra 1918-1919 (Box 4)
  - Uppman, Theodor (Box 4)
  - Van ?, Isaac (Box 4)
  - Van Beinum, Eduard (Box 4)
  - Van Deursen, Hardin (Box 4)
  - Van Gordon, Cyrena (Box 4)
  - Van Kirk, Mary (Box 4)
  - Varnay, Astrid (Box 4)
  - Vidas, Raoul (Box 4)
  - Virovai, Robert (Box 4)
  - Virtuosi di Roma (Box 4)
  - Von Karajan, Herbert (Box 4)
  - Vronsky, Vitya (Box 4)
    (see Babin, Victor)
  - Wagner, Charles L. (Box 4)
  - Wallenstein, Alfred (Box 4)
  - Warenskjold, Dorothy (Box 4)
  - Warfield, William (Box 4)
  - Warren, Leonard (Box 4)
  - Watt, Charles E. (Box 4)
  - Welitch, Ljuba (Box 4)
  - Welsh, Bill (Box 4)
  - Westminster Choir (Box 4)
    (see J. F. Williamson)
  - Whitehill, Clarence (Box 4)
  - Widdop, Walter, 2 photographs (Box 4)
  - Wilkins, Marie (Box 4)
  - Williamson, J. F., 2 photographs (Box 4)
  - Witherspoon, Herbert (Box 4)
  - Wolfe, James (Box 4)
  - Wolff, Ernst Victor (Box 4)
  - Yeend, Frances (Box 4)
  - York, Francis L., 2 photographs (Box 4)
  - Zeisler, Fannie Bloomfield (Box 4)
  - Zimbalist, Efrem (Box 4)
  - Zirato (?) (Box 4)
  - Oversized photographs; contents listed above (Box 5)
- Photograph Album
  (The contents of the album were removed and put into folders; the album belonged to Charles Sink but probably was not compiled by him; some of the photographs were addressed to Miss Helen White)
  - Unidentified (Box 6)
  - Adams, Maude, 2 photographs (Box 6)
  - Alves, C. Katie (Box 6)
  - Arro, Mary (Box 6)
  - Barrymore, Maurice (Box 6)
  - Bauer, Harold, 2 photographs (Box 6)
  - Beeth, Lola (Box 6)
  - Berthald, Barron (Box 6)
  - Bispham, David (Box 6)
  - Bosetti, Hermine (Box 6)
  - Burgess, Neil (Box 6)
  - Burroughs, Marie (Box 6)
  - Campanari, G. (Box 6)
  - Campanari, Sig. (Box 6)
  - Campanini, Halo (Box 6)
  - Carreno, Teresa (Box 6)
  - Carter, Leslie (Box 6)
  - Caruso, Enrico (Box 6)
  - Cook, Augustus (Box 6)
    (see also Kidder, Kathryn)
  - Coquelin, C. (Box 6)
  - Cowles, Eugene (Box 6)
  - Crane, W. H. (Box 6)
  - Davis, Jessie Bartlett (Box 6)
  - Del Puente, Guiseppe (Box 6)
  - Dixey, Henry E., 2 photographs (Box 6)
  - Drouet, Robert, 3 photographs (Box 6)
  - Dufft, Carl E. (Box 6)
  - Duse, Leonora (Box 6)
  - Elliott, Maxine (Box 6)
  - Faversham, William (Box 6)
  - Feinhals, Fritz, 2 photographs (Box 6)
  - Feldenrust, P. (Box 6)
    (item had been attached to verso of photo of ? Joseff)
  - Fischer, Arthur William (Box 6)
  - Fischer, Emil (Box 6)
  - Fox, Della (Box 6)
  - Frabadelo, A. de (Box 6)
  - Gericke, Wilhelm (Box 6)
  - Gigli, Beniamino (Box 6)
  - Gilbert, Mrs. G. H. (Box 6)
  - Goodwin, Nat C. (Box 6)
  - Heinrich, Max (Box 6)
  - Hofmann, Josef (Box 6)
  - Irving, Henry (Box 6)
  - Jefferson, Josef (Box 6)
  - Joseff (Box 6)
  - Juch, Emma (Box 6)
  - Kidder, Kathryn (Box 6)
  - Kreisler, Fritz (Box 6)
  - Kubelik, Jan (Box 6)
  - Lasully (?), T. or J. (Box 6)
  - MacDowell, Melbourne, 2 photographs (Box 6)
  - Marlowe, Julia, 2 photographs (Box 6)
  - Morena, Bertha (Box 6)
  - Mosse, Felis (Box 6)
  - Nading, Jane (Box 6)
  - Nethersole, Olga (Box 6)
  - Pendelton, Lillian Blauvelt (Box 6)
  - Plancon, Pol (Box 6)
  - Preuse-Matzenauer, Margarete (Box 6)
  - Rehan, Ada (Box 6)
  - Reszke, Edouard de (Box 6)
  - Reszke, Jean de (Box 6)
  - Rhea, 2 photographs (Box 6)
  - Robson, Stuart, 2 photographs (Box 6)
  - Saliza, Alli or Olli (Box 6)
  - Scharwenka, H. (Box 6)
  - Schillings, Max (Box 6)
    (see Gigli, Beniamino)
  - Schueöker, Edmund (Box 6)
  - Schueöker, Heinrich (Box 6)
  - Scotti, A. (Box 6)
  - Seidl(bys?), Anton (Box 6)
  - Sembrich, Marcella (Box 6)
  - Stein, Gertrude May (Box 6)
  - Tauscher, Johanna Gadski (Box 6)
  - Tavany, M.B. (Box 6)
  - Ternina, Milka (Box 6)
  - Tlaicheisger, Thila (Box 6)
  - Vokrens, E. M. (Box 6)
  - Wagner, Siegfried (Box 6)
  - Willard, E. S. (Box 6)
  - Wilson, Francis (Box 6)
  - Woodruff, Henry (Box 6)
  - Yournetz, Marcel, 2 photographs (Box 6)
  - Ysaye, Eugene (Box 6)
  - Zerrahn, Carl, 2 photographs (Box 6)
Related Material
The political and personal papers of Charles A. Sink have been separately cataloged.